<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ksrof&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Ksrof&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 08:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Anew</title>
      <link>/posts/starting-anew/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/starting-anew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Normally people do this kind of thing on their new year&amp;rsquo;s resolutions, but since I do not like
to postpone stuff here I am, starting a new blog from the ashes of the previous one. But why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well it&amp;rsquo;s quite simple, I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed a certain pattern that keeps emerging in the things I personally
do. When I have an idea, i.e. a blog, I tend to prototype something simple but functional, then
I iterate over the base idea to add more functionalities to it, and then when everything is working,
instead of using it to serve the purpose it was built for, I take an entirely different path and try to
make it even more perfect, by either revamping the whole user interface or &lt;em&gt;the thing that happened
this time&lt;/em&gt;, trying to build a fully fledged static site generator to post my shit. Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m quite a
DIY guy. But the problem does not reside in the idea of making a static site generator, nope, the thing
is that I subconsciously see what I&amp;rsquo;ve just created as something incomplete, and my focus shifts
entirely into creating that static site generator. I bet you can see the problem now, the feat that I
was trying to accomplish is not something that you do in a weekend, unless you&amp;rsquo;re ThePrimeagen. So I&amp;rsquo;ve
decided to still do that project because it&amp;rsquo;s a topic I&amp;rsquo;m interested in, but I will shove my perfectionism
up my arse and use &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;hugo&lt;/a&gt;, which in all honesty it&amp;rsquo;s mind-blowingly great, to keep
throwing content out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From now on you can expect one article per week, all related to programming, and since I want to use
this blog as a way to learn new stuff, many of the posts that you&amp;rsquo;ll find will be related to weekend
projects that I have built, tech that I want to try out, or when I feel a bit philosophical, my point
of view about a certain topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your time, ksrof out.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
